Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 6; 7.4 cubic ft.
  - Louisville Softball NCAA Post Season Guide, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Northwestern Softball Media Guide and Post Season Guide, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Softball Media Guide, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Syracuse Men's Lacrosse Media Guide, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - UAlbany Men's Lacrosse Media Guide, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - UAlbany Women's Lacrosse Media Guide, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - University of Virginia Men's Lacrosse Media Guide, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 2005-2006 UAlbany Media Guides: Men's Basketball, Women's Tennis, Men's Lacrosse, Women's Golf, Track and Field, Women's Basketball (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - America East and NCAA Materials, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Football, Wagner vs. Robert Morris, 2006 October 7 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball Media Guide, 2006 November 21
  - Women's Basketball Media Guide, 2006 November 21
  - Connecticut NCAA Championship Media Guide, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Football Guides, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Johns Hopkins Men's Lacrosse Media Guide, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball, NCAA Tournament, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Monmouth Football Programs, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NCAA Division I Men's Basketball Championship Media Guides, Programs, and Scores, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Stony Brook Football Guides and Programs, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - UAlbany Men's Lacrosse Media Guide, America East Conference Champions, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Wagner Football Guides, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Women's Lacrosse Media Guides, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Basketball, Game Day Program, Women vs. UMBC, Men vs. Maine, Men vs. Stony Brook, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Men's Basketball Media Guide, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Sporting News Magazine, College Basketball Preview, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Football Media Guides, 2006-2010 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - University at Albany Magazine, 2007 Fall (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - University at Albany Magazine, Jamar Wilson Cover, 2007 Spring (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Baseball Championship Guide, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Men's Lacrosse Media Guide/ Championships Guide, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Field Hockey Media Guide, 2007
  - Gameday and Sports Illustrated Publication, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Men's Basketball, NCAA Tournament, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Men's Soccer Media Guide, 2007
  - National Invitation Tournament Men's Basketball Media Guide, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Opponent Men's Lacrosse Media Guides: Johns Hopkins, Loyola, Syracuse, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Volleyball Media Guide, 2007
  - Women's Field Hockey Media Guide, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Women's Soccer Media Guide, 2007
  - America East Women's Basketball Media Guide, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Holy Cross Women's Basketball Media Guide, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Men's Lacrosse Media Guides, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball Media Guide Draft, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Women's Gold Media Guide, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Women's Tennis Media Guide, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Football Game Day Programs, 2007; 2011 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hall of Fame Induction and Great Dane Awards Programs, 2007; 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Inside Lacrosse Magazine, Mike Banks Cover, 2008 October (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - America East Men's Basketball Championship Program and Post Season Guide, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Football, The Troy Record, " UAlbany Finishes Unbeaten", 2008 November 16 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - America East field Hockey Championship, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - UMBC Men's Lacrosse Media Guide, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Football Media Guide, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Men's Soccer Media Guides, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Syracuse Men's Lacrosse Roster Card Programs, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Basketball, America East Conference Tournament Game Notes, 2008-2011 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Women's Basketball Media Guides, 2008-2009; 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Women's Gold Media Guide, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 42'rd UAlbany Invitational, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Cross Country Media Guide, 2009 September 25
  - Hockey Media Guide, 2009 September 25
  - Men's Soccer Media Guide, 2009 September 25
  - Volleyball Media Guide, 2009 September 25
  - Women's Soccer Media Guide, 2009 September 25
  - Men's Basketball Media Guide, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - UAlbany Basketball Game Day Guides, 2009-2011 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Men's Lacrosse, Hartford vs. Albany Program, 2010 March 31 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - W, Soccer Media Guide, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Men's Basketball Yearbooks, 2010-2012 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - UAlbany Alumni Career Panel, 2011 February 8 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Syracuse Men's Lacrosse Program and Media Guide, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Men's Basketball Media Guide, 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - The Business Review, Interview with Bob Ford, 2012 October 5-2012 October 11 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - America East Championship, Men's Basketball and Women's Basketball Media Guide, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Women's Basketball, Senior Day, 2012-2013 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - America East Men's Basketball Post Season Notes, 2013 March 8-2013 March 10 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - UAlbany Business Magazine, Scholar Athlete Success Issue, 2013 Spring (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Football Program, UAlbany vs. Central Connecticut, 2013 September 21 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Football Program, UAlbany vs. Towson, 2013 October 19 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Richmond Spiders Football Game, 2013 November 2 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Football, UAlbany vs. Maine, Game Notes and Program, 2013 November 9 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Football, UAlbany vs. New Hampshire, Including Program and Speech by Bob Ford, 2013 November 16 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Program, 2013 November (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Football, Bob Ford Field Inaugural Season Guide, UAlbany vs. Rhode Island and New Hampshire, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Men's Basketball NCAA Tournament Notes, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - NCAA Women's Basketball Championship Program, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Women's Basketball NCAA Tournament Notes, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Women's Basketball NCAA Tournament Notes, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Athletic Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony Programs, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Basketball Programs, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Stony Brook Men's Basketball America East Championship Guide and Statistics, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - UAlbany Men's Basketball, America East Tournament and NCAA Tournament Game Notes, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - UAlbany Men's and Women's Basketball vs. Vermont Catamounts, 2014 February 1 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Lacrosse Magazine, Lyle Thompson, Preseason Player of the year, 2014 February (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - America East Men's Basketball Championship Notes, Stony Brook vs. Albany, 2014 March 15 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Football Program, Albany vs. Holy Cross, 2014 August 30 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Football Spring Game Program and Notes, 2014 March 19 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Football, UAlbany vs. Central Connecticut, 2014 September 6 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Albany Great Danes Football of Rhode Island Rams, 2014 September 2014 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Football Program, UAlbany vs. Columbia, 2014 September 27 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Football Program, Albany vs. JMU, 2014 October 4 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Football Program, UAlbany vs. Colgate, 2014 October 25 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Football Program, Albany vs. UD, 2014 November 8 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Program, 2014 December (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Basketball Championship, America East Conference, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Football Game Day Guide, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Football Media Guide, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Football Programs and Game Notes, Colgate and Delaware, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Football, Villanova Program and Itinerary, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Lacrosse, The 14th Annual Tewaaraton Award, The Year of the Oneida, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - NCAA Women's Basketball Championship, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Softball Regionals Program and Information, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - West Virginia Women's Basketball NCAA Tournament Guide, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Athletics Annual Report, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Basketball Game Programs and Notes, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball and Women's Basketball, Game Day Guides (1 of 2), 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball and Women's Basketball, Game Day Guides ( 2 of 2), 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Athletics Annual Reports, 2014-2017 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - UAlbany Men's Lacrosse Media Guides, 2014; 2016-2018 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Men's Basketball, Albany vs. Oklahoma, Final Four, NCAA Tournament, Game Notes and Program, 2015 March (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Men's Basketball NCAA Second and Third Rounds Program, 2015 March (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Division I Women's Basketball Championship, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Football Media Day, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Men's Lacrosse NCAA Championship Preliminary Rounds Guide, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - NCAA Division I Men's Basketball Championship, Second and Third Rounds, Columbus, Official Program, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - NCAA Division I Women's Soccer Championship Game Notes, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - NCAA Men's Basketball Championship Program, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Handout, 2015-2016 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Women's Basketball Yearbook, 2015-2016 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Women's Soccer Game Notes, 2015-2016 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Lacrosse, The Tewaaraton Award Programs, 2015; 2017 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball Media Guides, 2015-2017 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball Championship Programs, 2015; 2017 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 2016 Great Dane Awards Guide, 2016 May 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 2016 Cross Country/ Track and Field Wall of Fame Induction, 2016 October 15 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Men's Lacrosse Yearbook and Media Day Guide, 2016 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball Championship Program, 2016 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - UAlbany Football Promotion Pamphlet, 2016 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - MAAC Directory, 2016-2017 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - UAlbany Office of Compliance Services, Compliance Manual, 2016-2017 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Women's Basketball Media Guides, 2016-2018 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Great Dane Athletic Club Guides, 2016; 2018-2019 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Recognition Weekend, President's Annual for Leadership, 2017 April 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball Championship, UAlbany vs UConn, 2017 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - UAlbany Basketball Fan Guide, 2017-2018 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Football Media Guide, 2018 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Men's Lacrosse Media Guide, 2018 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - UAlbany Athletics Annual Report, 2018-2019 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - University at Albany America East Inaugural Year, "Autograph Notebook", Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1979-2014; 7; 10.4 cubic ft.
  This collection contains news clippings related to the athletic activities of the University At Albany's student body and the New York Giant's summer training camp. Content includes various sport scores, news stories about players/teams, and the New York Giant's training camp on campus.
  - Football News Clippings, 1979 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Football News Clippings, ca. 1970s-1980s (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Football News Clippings, ca. 1980s (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Special Olympics, 1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
  - Hitchcock Press News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Wrestling News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 10)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 11)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1997 (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
  - Division One, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 12)
  - Empire State Games, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 13)
  - Times Union-Giants in Training, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 14)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 15)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 16)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 17)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 18)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 19)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 20)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 21)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, ca. 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 22)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 23)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 24)
  - Times Union-Giants Training Camp at Albany, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 25)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 26)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 27)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 28)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 29)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 30)
  - Women's Basketball News Clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 31)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 32)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2001-2004 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 33)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2001-2004 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 34)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2002 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
  - Football News Clippings, 2002 (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball Clippings, 2002 (Oversized 2, Folder 3)
  - Football News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 35)
  - Football News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 36)
  - Field Hockey News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 37)
  - Football News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 38)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Volleyball News Clipping, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Women's and Men's Cross Country News Clippings, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Women's Track and Field News Clippings, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Men's and Women's Soccer News Clippings, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Tennis News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball and Volleyball News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - Golf News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 4)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 6)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2003-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 7)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 8)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 9)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 10)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 11)
  - Softball News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - Men's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 10)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 11)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 12)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 13)
  - Field Hockey News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 14)
  - Men's and Women Cross Country News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 15)
  - Men's Track and Field News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 16)
  - Indoor Track News Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 17)
  - Times News Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 18)
  - Men's and Women's Soccer News Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 19)
  - Women's Basketball News Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 2, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 2, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 3, Folder 1)
  - Baseball News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 3, Folder 2)
  - Football News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 3, Folder 3)
  - Softball News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 21)
  - Men's Soccer News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 22)
  - Volleyball News Clipping, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 23)
  - Women's Soccer New Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 24)
  - Football News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 25)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 26)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 27)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 28)
  - Times Union-Giants Training Camp, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 29)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 30)
  - Athletic Department News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 31)
  - Women's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 32)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 33)
  - Men's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 34)
  - Men's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 35)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 36)
  - Field Hockey News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 37)
  - Men's Cross Country News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 38)
  - Women's Outdoor Track News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 39)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 40)
  - Women's Basketball News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 41)
  - Women's Basketball News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 42)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 43)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Oversized 3, Folder 4)
  - Indoor Track and Field News Clippings, 2004-2006 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 44)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, 2005 (Oversized 3, Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings-Winter/Spring, 2005 (Oversized 3, Folder 6)
  - Athletic News Clippings-Winter/Spring, 2005 (Oversized 3, Folder 7)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 45)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 46)
  - Softball News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 47)
  - Women's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 48)
  - Baseball News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 49)
  - Department News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 50)
  - Outdoor Track and Field, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 51)
  - Men's Lacorsse News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 52)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 53)
  - Winter/Spring News Clippings, 2005-2006 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 54)
  - Winter/Spring News Clippings, 2005-2006 (Oversized 4, Folder 1)
  - Winter/Spring News Clippings, 2005-2006 (Oversized 4, Folder 2)
  - Winter/Spring News Clippings, 2005-2006 (Oversized 4, Folder 3)
  - NCAA News Clippings, 2006 (Oversized 4, Folder 4)
  - Rape Scandal News Clippings, 2006 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2006 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2006-2007 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2006-2007 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2006-2007 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Articles Part 1-LAX, Tennis,Soccer, Field Hockey, Women's Basketball, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Articles Part 2-Misc, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Articles Part 3-Softball,Baseball,Football, 2006-2007 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - The Record, 2008 (Oversized 5, Folder 1)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 10)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 11)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 12)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 2)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 3)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 4)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 6)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 7)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Oversized 5, Folder 8)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 13)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 14)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 15)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 16)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 17)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 18)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 19)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 20)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 21)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2008-2010 (Box 4 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)